Hsiang-Chun Wang

Graduate Institute of Communication Engineering National Taiwan University, Taipei, Taiwan Work Email: Personal Email: Website Google Scholar r11942158@ntu.edu.tw wang02052000@gmail.com

Research Interests

My research is broadly focused on deep learning and its applications to computer vision and robotics. The work I am doing is enhancing reinforcement learning (RL) algorithms by drawing insights from breakthroughs in computer vision. Recently, I have been interested in deep learning's interpretability and fairness problems, and I am trying program synthesis as a solution.

Education

Sep 2022 - Present	M.S. in Communications Engineering National Taiwan University (NTU) Advisors: Prof. Shao-Hua Sun
Sep 2018 - Aug 2022	B.Eng. in Information Engineering Shanghai Jiao Tong University (SJTU) Advisor: Prof. Jiaxin Ding

Publications

Diffusion Model-Augmented Behavioral Cloning

Hsiang-Chun Wang, Shang-Fu Chen, Ming-Hao Hsu, Chun-Mao Lai, Shao-Hua Sun Frontiers4LCD Workshop at International Conference on Machine Learning (ICML) 2023

Diffusion Model-Augmented Behavioral Cloning

Hsiang-Chun Wang, Shang-Fu Chen, Ming-Hao Hsu, Chun-Mao Lai, Shao-Hua Sun *ArXiv Preprint*

Experience

Apr 2022 - Now	Master Researcher at NTU, Taiwan. Investigated ideas to enhance reinforcement learning algorithms.
Nov 2021 - Jun 2022	<u>Undergraduate Thesis</u> at SJTU, China. Research ideas for identifying actions in tennis matches and develop software to extract essential moments from game footage.
Jun 2020 - Sep 2020	Research Intern at SJTU, China. Explored solutions to find embedding vectors in GPS trajectory data.
Sep 2018 - Aug 2019	Engineering Job at SJTU, China. Developed a technique to identify armor plates

Coursework

Linear Algebra
Machine Learning
Deep Learning for Computer Vision
Visual Localization and Sensing

Image Processing and Analysis Video Coding and Communication Computer Network Reinforcement Learning (ongoing)